one-time-offer.com 2011-06-28

# Webloyalty

## Privacy Policy

The following sets forth webloyalty.com’s practices of collection, use and disclosure of information gathered from online visitors to the webloyalty.com website.  This website is owned and operated by Webloyalty.com, Inc., 101 Merritt 7, 4th Floor, Norwalk, Connecticut 06851.  For information on how our members’ personal information is collected use and/or disclosed, please review the privacy policy for the program. 

### About Webloyalty's privacy practices:

**Below, you will find the answers to the following questions:**

  * [How can you access the information we have collected about you? ](http://www.webloyalty.com/private_policy.html#7)
  * [How do we transfer and store data received from residents outside of the United States? ](http://www.webloyalty.com/private_policy.html#8) 
  * [What can you do if you have a question or concern about this policy and who within our organization is accountable for compliance?](http://www.webloyalty.com/private_policy.html#9)

**What information do we collect about you?**

We automatically collect the following information from you: the IP address of the computer you are using, your domain name, your browser, your operating system, the navigation path that brought you to our site, aggregate information on what pages you access or visit and user-specific information about the pages you access or visit.  In addition, if you volunteer such information, we will also collect visitor survey information and any site registrations you may complete.  Finally, if you volunteer it, we will collect certain personally identifiable information, including, but not limited to, your name, your email address, your telephone number, your mailing address and your employer (collectively “Personal Information”). 

Our pages may use “cookies”.  Cookies record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, help ensure visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

**How do we use that information?**

We use the information we collect for feedback purposes, for a statistical analysis of visitor’s behavior, for product development or enhancement, for content improvement, and/or to customize content and layout of our site. If you have opted in to such use, Personal Information may be added to our databases and used for future contact regarding new products and services, upcoming events and/or customer service.  If you do not want to receive additional communications from us about our other products and/or services, please let us know by contacting the General Counsel as set forth below. 

**With whom do we share that information?**

We may also make certain information and/or Personal Information about our visitors available to third parties for the following purposes: we may disclose information and/or Personal Information to vendors who facilitate and/or support our website and/or our email transmissions (including, but not limited to, vendors who assist our suppression to comply with the CAN SPAM Act of 2003), and we may disclose information to entities to whom we are legally required to disclose information and/or to protect our rights or safety or the rights or safety of our visitors or any third party. 

In addition, if you have opted in to such use, from time to time, we may make the Personal Information you voluntarily submitted available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your Personal Information with other companies or organizations, please let us know by contacting the General Counsel as set forth below.  

In the unlikely event Webloyalty and/or substantially all of its assets are sold, information, including Personal Information, about visitors to this website may be one of the transferred assets.  Such information would remain subject to any pre-existing privacy policy (unless you consent to the use of such information otherwise). 

This website may contain third party advertising and/or may link to other websites.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices, terms of use and/or the content of such other third party websites or advertisements.

**How will you know if we make changes to this policy?**

From time to time, we may use information and/or Personal Information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice.  If our collection, use and/or disclosure practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new practices.  If you are concerned about how your information and/or Personal Information are used, you should check back at our website periodically.  Your continued use of this website following the posting of changes to these terms shall be deemed your consent to any such changes. Such changes will be evidenced by a change in the effective date for this policy set forth above.  We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. 

**Are children permitted to visit our website?**

Our website is not intended for children under thirteen. If you are under thirteen, you may use our website only with the permission of a parent or guardian.

**How is your information secured?**

All information and Personal Information collected is stored in a secured environment which provides for both physical and technical safeguards, including, but not limited to, firewalls, token authentication, application proxies, monitoring technology and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data.  Please be advised, however, that no data security methodology is entirely secure.  You should take reasonable steps to protect yourself against unauthorized access to your information and Personal Information.    

**How can you access the information we have collected about you?**

We provide you with access to the Personal Information we have collected about you.  In addition, you may request that your Personal Information be corrected if you believe it is not accurate. If you wish to access your Personal Information you should contact our General Counsel as set forth below. 

**How do we transfer and store data received from residents outside of the United States?  **

If you are visiting our site from outside of the United States, you acknowledge that we may host or store data you provide to us outside of your country of residence; in particular, data may be hosted or stored in the United States of America. While we take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of personal data that you disclose online.  By providing us with any personal and/or sensitive data through this site, you accept the inherent security implications of online communications.  If you are concerned about the international data transfer and/or the security of your personal or sensitive data submitted online, please do not send us any personal and/or sensitive data through this site.   

**What can you do if you have a question or concern about this policy and who within our organization is accountable for compliance?**

If you feel that we are not complying with our stated privacy policy, you may contact us via regular mail at Webloyalty.com, Inc., 101 Merritt 7, 4th Floor, Norwalk, Connecticut 06851, Att: General Counsel.  We are responsible for the Personal Information under our control, and we have designated our General Counsel as the responsible party for ensuring our compliance with this policy and with any applicable privacy legislation.
